# Max Su

<del>- -</del>

Senior Full-stack Developer

Github: https://github.com/slarkjm0803

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/max-su-019199212/

Email: slarkjm@outlook.com, maxsu0803@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I am a highly skilled full stack developer who has 10 years experiences in software development. Self-motivated problem solver looking to drive technical projects from design, implementation, deployment. I worked on blockchain projects ago with Solidity, web3.js, ether.js Also, I minted many images and game items for their dapps with complicated logic and nowadays, I mainly worked on Python, Django, laravel, mysql, Nosql, React.js, vue.js, vuetify etc as a full-stack developer.

So I believe I am the most suitable guy for your project.

Also, I am familiar with GitHub project management and like to work with team guys.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2019~2021

## Back-End Developer (Donjon-Smit, LLC)

Domain - https://portal.donjon-smit.com/#/

- Worked as backend developer so I deployed the project to gcp instance using Jenkins from github repository
- Set the database on gcp and connected to gcp instance and managed all process fully
- Structured the mysql database and queries with complicated logic
- Completed the 8 role process in middleware and response the backend apis to frontend
  Sometimes I supported the frontend (vuetify) since I am also familiar with vuetify framework.

2018~2019

# Solidity Developer (DICEUS)

Domain – Digitalax.xyz

- Developed the Dapp using solidity and next.js, fauna database, node.js
- Issue NFT for game item and pictures and login using metamask and Arkane wallet
- Sometimes supported the backend with node.js and fauna database.

2016~2018

### Full-Stack Developer (DxMinds Technologies Inc)

- Developed the AI bots using python and scrapping many data from API and some websites.
- Used private network for the application and deployed to AWS for source code

2011~2020

## Full-Stack Developer (Avatar Property & Casualty Insurance)

- Worked as full-stack developer so I managed whole project system like deploy to the server (Amazon) from github.
- Mastered reinsurance logic with projects and developed back and front end sides using Laravel and React.js.
- Managed very complicated mysql database queries and supported several team guys

2010~2011

# Software Engineer (IBM Internship)

- Developed desktop apps using C++, MFC

- Mainly for company apps so it was local apps

# **EDUCATION**

2010~2011 Bachelors, Information Technology (University of Seoul) (2010.09)

SKILLS LANGUAGES

•	Python	Expert
•	Mysql	Expert
•	NoSql	Expert
•	Solidity	Expert
•	Django	Expert
•	Ethers.js	Expert
•	Laravel	Expert
•	Vue.js	Expert
•	React.js	Expert
•	Github	Expert

Korean Native English Advanced Chinese Native